https://www.bgsu.edu/general-counsel/university-policies/web-privacy-policy.html

Skip to main content
We use cookies to provide you with the best experience and to help improve our website. View Privacy Statement
Majors and Programs
Orientation (SOAR)
Title IX
We Are One Team (WA1T)
Services
Interlibrary Loan (ILL)
ScholarWorks@BGSU
Ask Us!
Dean of Students
Dining (on-campus)
Independent Falcon Network
Information Technology Services (ITS)
Majors and Programs
Orientation (SOAR)
Title IX
We Are One Team (WA1T)
Services
Interlibrary Loan (ILL)
ScholarWorks@BGSU
Ask Us!
Dean of Students
Dining (on-campus)
Independent Falcon Network
Information Technology Services (ITS)
3341-6- 49 BGSU Web Privacy Policy
Applicability:
All University units
Responsible Unit:
The Vice President for Finance and Administration
Policy Administrator:
The Office of the Chief Information Officer
(A) Policy Statement and Purpose
Bowling Green State University (BGSU) uses best industry practices for website user privacy. This policy shall guide developers and users regarding website privacy guidelines for BGSU.
(B) Policy Scope
This Policy applies to any person subject to a university Policy including but not limited to, (a) students, (b) faculty, (b) staff, (b) alumni, (e) volunteers, (f) visitors, and (g) others who provide services or act under the name of the university, including contractors, vendors and consultants.
Each university Policy should set forth, in the “Policy Scope” section, the members of the university community who are subject to the policy.
(C) Policy
Personal Information
(a) At times BGSU may require contact information (i.e. name, address, email address, ZIP code and country of residence) to be provided when requesting information about college programs and services. This contact information is used to provide you with the specific information you requested. Occasionally, you may receive subsequent notifications of important information regarding the programs or services for which you made your initial inquiry.
(b) A user’s browser sends us a variety of information such as IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser session, SSL Encryption and URL (Uniform Resource Locator). This information lets us know how the user is finding our site and which pages they have visited most often. All of this is used to improve the navigation of the site and to make it more useful for our visitors.
(c) In addition to the information provided by the browser, we also collect information that the user voluntarily provides when filling out any information request or an application for one of the programs featured on our site.
Online Advertising
(a) Certain BGSU websites utilize the Google AdWords marketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google). Third-party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the BGSU website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
(b) Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to them using the Google Ad Preferences page found here: https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated. In addition, you can opt out of interest-based advertising on this same webpage.
Consent
By using the official BGSU website, you consent to the collection and use of information discussed above as described in this policy.
Fund Raising, Solicitation, and Sales Rules for Student Organizations
Office of General Counsel308 McFall CenterBowling Green, OH 43403-0012
419-372-0464
Fax: 419-372-8700
gencounsel@bgsu.edu
